<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="truthCrazy"> //Truth - Crazy (testArray8)
        <item>What’s the dirtiest thought you’ve ever had?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought of killing someone?</item>
        <item>What sexual activity do you consider totally off limits?</item>
        <item>Of the people in this room, who do you consider the sluttiest?</item>
        <item>What’s the most embarrassing thing your parents have caught you doing?</item>
        <item>What’s the weirdest thing you’ve done when you were alone?</item>
        <item>What’s the biggest secret you’ve ever kept from your parents?</item>
        <item>What’s the biggest lie you’ve ever told without getting caught?</item>
        <item>What do you like most and least about your own appearance?xxx</item>
        <item>What’s the craziest thing you’ve ever done to attract a crush?</item>
        <item>What’s your biggest sexual fear?</item>
        <item>What would you change about your life if you could?</item>
        <item>If you could make one wish right this second, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What three adjectives best describe your vagina/penis?</item>
        <item>What’s sexual milestone has been most memorable for you so far?</item>
        <item>What’s the weirdest thing you’ve ever done in front of the mirror?</item>
        <item>What would you guess your parents’ favorite sexual position is, and why?</item>
        <item>What did you think about the first (or last) time you masturbated?</item>
        <item>What’s the most surprising thing that’s ever turned you on?</item>
        <item>What’s the most disgusting thing you’ve ever done?</item>
        <item>What’s the most disturbing fantasy or dream you’ve ever had?</item>
        <item>What’s the meanest thing you’ve ever said to someone?</item>
        <item>What’s the cruelest thing you’ve ever done to a friend?</item>
        <item>How do you really feel about anal sex?</item>
        <item>Do you ever catch yourself thinking about doing it with someone of the same sex?</item>
        <item>What’s the most number of times you’ve ever masturbated within one week?</item>
        <item>What was the craziest thing that has happened to you in a mall?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought of cheat on your boyfriend / girlfriend?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied to your partner to avoid an intimate moment, for teemu, say that you feel sick?</item>
        <item>What was the most disgusting joke ever played with someone?</item>
        <item>What’s your wildest fantasy?</item>
        <item>Have you ever peed in a pool?</item>
        <item>What is the dumbest thing you’ve said your partner while on intimacy?</item>
        <item>Which of the people who are in this game, considered to have the best body?</item>
        <item>How long is your penis?</item>
        <item>Do you have any fetishes?</item>
        <item>Do you have any irrational fears?</item>
        <item>What’s the worst thing you’ve ever stolen?</item>
        <item>Have you ever masturbated anywhere inappropriate?</item>
        <item>What’s the strangest porn you’ve ever got off on?</item>
        <item>Do you like getting tortured?</item>
        <item>Where is the strangest place you’ve used the bathroom?</item>
        <item>How do you feel about sex in groups?</item>
        <item>How do you feel about cuckold?</item>
        <item>Have you ever taken it in the butt or would you?</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy rough or slow sex?</item>
        <item>Do you like blowjobs?</item>
        <item>Which races do you prefer?</item>
        <item>Have you ever farted in an elevator?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought about your parents naked?</item>
        <item>Have you ever tasted ear wax?</item>
        <item>Would you have sex with animals?</item>
        <item>Would you have sex with robots?</item>
        <item>What is your deepest darkest fear?</item>
        <item>Have you ever crapped your pants since you were a child?</item>
        <item>Who is the person you most regret kissing?</item>
        <item>What is the grossest thing that has come out of your body?</item>
    </array>
</resources>