<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="truthTeens"> //Truth - Teens (testArray4)
        <item>What would you do if you were the opposite sex for a month?</item>
        <item>What is the most expensive thing you have stolen?</item>
        <item>How old were you when you had your first kiss</item>
        <item>What is your deepest darkest fear?</item>
        <item>Who is the most beautiful person here?</item>
        <item>What is the most embarrassing photo you have on your phone?</item>
        <item>What is the weirdest thing you have done for a boyfriend or girlfriend?</item>
        <item>What is your most embarrassing vomit story?</item>
        <item>What is one thing that you never want your parents to know about?</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a crush on a teacher?</item>
        <item>Have you ever picked your nose and ate it?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied to answer a truth question?</item>
        <item>Where is the weirdest place that you’ve ever gone solo?</item>
        <item>Have you ever been attracted to the same sex?</item>
        <item>What was it like going down on someone the first time?</item>
        <item>How often do you trim down there?</item>
        <item>Have you lost your virginity?</item>
        <item>What’s your favorite body part on a girl?</item>
        <item>Last time you cried?</item>
        <item>What’s something your mom doesn’t know about you?</item>
        <item>What is the dumbest thing you’ve ever said?</item>
        <item>What’s your biggest insecurity?</item>
        <item>What is something that is absolutely off-limits in the bedroom?</item>
        <item>When was the last time you got really angry?</item>
        <item>Fictional character that you have the biggest crush on?</item>
        <item>Who’s your current crush?</item>
        <item>Who’s the most boring person here?</item>
        <item>Did you ever dislike anyone in this group?</item>
        <item>Have you ever walked in on your parents doing it?</item>
        <item>Have you ever peed in the pool?</item>
        <item>Do you talk in your sleep?</item>
        <item>How would you rate your looks on a scale of 1 to 10?</item>
        <item>What was the last thing you texted?</item>
        <item>Do you pee in the shower?</item>
        <item>Do you have any silly nicknames?</item>
        <item>How many selfies do you take a day?</item>
        <item>What is the most awkward moment you’ve ever had on a date?</item>
        <item>What would you do on the perfect first date?</item>
        <item>If you could marry one teacher in the school, who would you pick and why?</item>
        <item>Pick one person in the group, what is some honest relationship advice you would give them?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied to your best friend?</item>
        <item>What are the three qualities you feel are most important in a friend?</item>
        <item>What would make you lie for your friend?</item>
        <item>How long have you gone without showering?</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a crush on anyone here?</item>
        <item>What do you think is your biggest physical flaw?</item>
        <item>Have you ever gone skinny dipping?</item>
        <item>What’s the dumbest thing you’ve ever done on a dare?</item>
        <item>If you weren’t here, what would you be doing?</item>
        <item>If you could switch places with someone for a day who would it be?</item>
        <item>If you could invent anything, what would it be?</item>
        <item>If you knew the world was about to end, what would you do?</item>
        <item>If you could be born again, who would you come back as?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you were invisible for a day?</item>
        <item>If your life were made into a movie who would play you?</item>
        <item>What would you do with a million dollars if you ever won the lottery?</item>
        <item>Have you ever stolen anything?</item>
        <item>What kids’ movie do you still secretly watch over and over?</item>
        <item>Which song are you embarrassed that you love?</item>
        <item>Have you ever been in trouble with the police?</item>
        <item>If you could go out on a date with a celebrity, who would it be?</item>
        <item>What happened on your most embarrassing date?</item>
        <item>Would you use a dating website?</item>
        <item>Are you obsessed with a celebrity?</item>
        <item>Would you go behind your bestie’s back with a crush?</item>
        <item>What are the three most important qualities you look for in a friend?</item>
        <item>What do you like most about your best friend?</item>
        <item>Can you go for weeks or even months without talking to your bestie?</item>
        <item>Did you have an imaginary friend?</item>
        <item>What’s your career ambition?</item>
        <item>Which subject do you hate the most?</item>
        <item>Are you into sports?</item>
        <item>Who is your favorite teacher and why?</item>
    </array>
</resources>