<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="truthAdults"> //Truth - Adults (testArray6)
        <item>What’s the most embarrassed you’ve ever been while having sex?</item>
        <item>Have you ever had sex with someone much younger or older than you?</item>
        <item>Have you ever been sexually attracted to someone you mentally knew was ugly?</item>
        <item>You wake up tomorrow as a woman – what dirty things do you do all day?</item>
        <item>What kind of fantasies do you have while you’re having sex?</item>
        <item>When’s the last time you touched yourself?</item>
        <item>Have you ever experimented with someone of the same gender?</item>
        <item>What was the most embarrassing moment of your life?</item>
        <item>Have you ever been humiliated?</item>
        <item>What is the strangest dream you’ve had in your life?</item>
        <item>Have you fallen in love with a friend of your partner?</item>
        <item>What do you think that your boyfriend / girlfriend thinks about marriage?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought of cheat on your boyfriend / girlfriend?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied to your partner to avoid an intimate moment, for teemu, say that you feel sick?</item>
        <item>What’s your wildest fantasy?</item>
        <item>Who (here) has a wrong partner or does not suit them?</item>
        <item>What is the dumbest thing you’ve said your partner while on intimacy?</item>
        <item>Which of the people who are in this game, considered to have the best body?</item>
        <item>If you could suddenly become invisible, what more naughty things you like to do?</item>
        <item>Have you ever sexted anyone?</item>
        <item>What is the most adventurous thing you’d want someone to do to you?</item>
        <item>Who do you most want to sleep with, out of everyone here?</item>
        <item>What is your sexual orientation?</item>
        <item>Where is the weirdest place that you’ve ever gone solo?</item>
        <item>What is your favorite "special" toy?</item>
        <item>When was your first kiss?</item>
        <item>Who was your best partner and why?</item>
        <item>When was the first time you came?</item>
        <item>Have you ever cheated?</item>
        <item>Have you ever wanted to cheat?</item>
        <item>How many people have you slept with?</item>
        <item>Who’s the hottest person at work?</item>
        <item>What would be more thrilling: angry sex or make-up sex?</item>
        <item>Who here are you most jealous of?</item>
        <item>Have you ever had an exciting dream about someone here</item>
        <item>When was a time you were so turned on you couldn’t stand it?</item>
        <item>Are you domestic or submissive?</item>
        <item>Most you’ve touched yourself in one day?</item>
        <item>Do you like a lot of foreplay?</item>
        <item>How often do you watch something naughty?</item>
        <item>When did you last go solo?</item>
        <item>Do you enjoy it when you get kissed on your neck?</item>
        <item>Have you ever thought about someone here in the shower?</item>
        <item>If you could buy anything with $50, what would you get?</item>
        <item>Did you ever fantasize about a teacher or an authority figure?</item>
        <item>Have you ever wanted to be tied you up?</item>
        <item>Have you ever given or received a lap dance?</item>
        <item>What’s the filthiest thing you’ve imagined doing to me?</item>
        <item>What was it like the first time someone went down on you?</item>
        <item>What’s the worst kiss you’ve ever been given?</item>
        <item>What’s your favorite body part on a guy?</item>
        <item>Most embarrassing crush you’ve ever had?</item>
        <item>What’s the hookup you regret the most?</item>
        <item>Have you ever faked it? When? Can you re-create it?</item>
        <item>Have you ever had a one night stand?</item>
        <item>Have you ever considered a threesome?</item>
        <item>Have you ever gotten a bikini wax?</item>
    </array>
</resources>