<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <array name="truthsKids"> //Truths - Kids (testArray2)
        <item>What is your least favorite thing about family gatherings?</item>
        <item>What is one thing that makes you relax?</item>
        <item>What is a bad habit that you have?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied about being sick so you could stay home from school?</item>
        <item>If anyone in your family could win an award for the most annoying, who would it be?</item>
        <item>What is the most embarrassing thing that has happened to you in front of a crowd?</item>
        <item>What was the worst gift you ever received?</item>
        <item>What is the one thing you are the most afraid of?</item>
        <item>Have you ever cheated on a test?</item>
        <item>What are your favorite pizza toppings?</item>
        <item>If you were granted three wishes, what would you wish for?</item>
        <item>What is something you find to be disgusting?</item>
        <item>Who was your favorite teacher in school?</item>
        <item>What makes you furious?</item>
        <item>If you were invisible what is something you would do?</item>
        <item>What was the name of your first crush?</item>
        <item>What is your biggest fear?</item>
        <item>If you could be someone else for a day who would you be?</item>
        <item>Who is the person you are the most jealous of and why?</item>
        <item>What’s your biggest regret?</item>
        <item>What’s one thing you would do if you waked up tomorrow as a bird?</item>
        <item>Have you ever peed in a pool?</item>
        <item>What do you hate and why?</item>
        <item>Who/what is someone/something that annoys you?</item>
        <item>What’s the worst thing that’s ever happened to you?</item>
        <item>When was the last time you cried and why?</item>
        <item>If you could live anywhere, where would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the last thing you searched on your phone?</item>
        <item>What is one embarrassing fact your friends should know about you?</item>
        <item>Do you believe in love at first sight?</item>
        <item>How do you feel about end pieces of a loaf of bread?</item>
        <item>What is the weirdest dream you’ve had?</item>
        <item>Do you cover your eyes during a scary part in a movie?</item>
        <item>Do you pick your nose?</item>
        <item>Do you sleep with a stuffed animal?</item>
        <item>Who do you like the least in this room and why?</item>
        <item>Do you ever admire yourself in the mirror?</item>
        <item>What would you do with $1,000?</item>
        <item>If you could be any celebrity, who would you be and why?</item>
        <item>What is the least favorite gift you’ve ever received?</item>
        <item>Do you keep a diary/journal?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied about your age?</item>
        <item>What is the grossest thing you’ve done today?</item>
        <item>Have you ever cried during a movie?</item>
        <item>What is something you wish you were better at?</item>
        <item>Have you ever broken something and blamed someone else?</item>
        <item>When was the last time you did something nice for someone else?</item>
        <item>Have you ever eaten a bug?</item>
        <item>Have you ever passed gas and blamed someone else?</item>
        <item>If you were marooned on an island with just a single person, who would you like it to be?</item>
        <item>If you woke up one day and notice that you are invisible, then what will be the first thing you would like to do?</item>
        <item>What was the nastiest joke you ever played on someone?</item>
        <item>If you could have anything in the world, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What do you like the most about everyone in the room?</item>
        <item>Have you ever lied to a teacher and what was it about?</item>
        <item>What’s the dumbest thing you ever said or did, around someone you liked?</item>
        <item>What was your most embarrassing farting moment?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet, or a sibling?</item>
        <item>Which are the funniest words you know?</item>
        <item>If Aladdin’s genie were to visit you, what would be your three wishes?</item>
        <item>What would be your new name, if you were allowed to choose one?</item>
        <item>When was the last time you were bored out of your brains?</item>
        <item>What is your secret superpower?</item>
        <item>If you get hold of a time machine, ’when’ would you like to go?</item>
        <item>Who is your best friend in the whole wide world?</item>
        <item>Have you cheated to win a game?</item>
        <item>What is one annoying habit of each person in the room?</item>
        <item>Worst grade you ever got on a paper?</item>
        <item>Most embarrassing thing anyone has ever said to you?</item>
        <item>Have you fallen asleep in class?</item>
        <item>Do you sleep with a nightlight?</item>
        <item>Did you brush your teeth this morning?</item>
        <item>Have you ever walked in your sleep?</item>
    </array>
</resources>